Finding Aid for the Rudolf Carnap Papers LSC.1029
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Articles and Reprints
  - Meyer, Adolf. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Meyer, G.L. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Meyer, Heinrich. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Meyer, Herman. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Meyers, R. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Meyerson, Emilie. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Michigan. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Mill, John Stuart. (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Miller, Cecil H. (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Miller, David L. (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Miller, Dickinson J. (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Mittasch, A. (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Moisil, C. (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Mokre-Graz, Hans. (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Molitor, Arnulf. (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Moller, Herbert. (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Moore, R.L. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Morecroft, John H. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Morgenroth-Gast, Ernst. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Moriguti, Sigeiti. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Morrison, Paul Guerrant. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Motwani, Kewal. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Moyal, J.E. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Mueller, Gustav. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Mulliken, Robert S. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Mullin, A.A. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Mumford, Lewis. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Munitz, Milton K. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Munk, Arthur W. (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - Murdock, George Peter. (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Nanda, D.N. (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - Naville, Andre. (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - Needham, Joseph. (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - Nelson, Raymond J. (Box 43, Folder 18)
  - Nemenyi, Paul. (Box 43, Folder 19)
  - Nernst, W. (Box 43, Folder 20)
  - Neumann, J.v. (Box 43, Folder 21)
  - Neurath, Olga. (Box 43, Folder 22)
  - Neurath, Otto. (Box 43, Folder 23)
  - Nissen, Ingjald. (Box 43, Folder 24)
  - Nohl, Herman. (Box 43, Folder 25)
  - Noll, W. (Box 43, Folder 26)
  - Northrop, F.S.C. (Box 43, Folder 27)
  - Oboukhoff, Nicholas M. (Box 43, Folder 28)
  - Ojemann, Ralph H. (Box 43, Folder 29)
  - Olberg, Hermann. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Onicescu, O. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Oppenheim, Felix. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Orthner, R. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Ostwald, Wilhelm. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Palagyi, Melchior. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Palter, Robert. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Paradies, F. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Patterson, Austin M. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Patterson, George W. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Perry, Charles M. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Perry, Charner M. (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Perry, J.W. (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Perry, R.B. (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Petrovic, G. (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Petzoldt, Joseph. (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Phalen, Adolf. (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Piaggio, H.T.H. (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Plaut, H.C. (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Popper, Karl R. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Prasad, Ganesh. (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Presburger, M. (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Pribram, R. (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Prinzhorn. (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Quesada, Ernesto. (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Rabel, Gabriele. (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Radl, E. (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Rand Corporation. (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Randall, J.H. (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Randall, John A. (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Rashevsky, N. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Rathke, Heinrich Bernhard. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Read, Allen Walker. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Rebhuhn, L. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Redfield, Robert. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Reenpaa, Yrjo. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Regan, Francis. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Regener, Erich. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Reichenbach, Hans (1 of 4). (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Reichenbach, Hans (2 of 4). (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Reichenbach, Hans (3 of 4). (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Reichenbach, Hans (4 of 4). (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Reichenbacher, Ernst. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Reichenstein, D. (Box 45, Folder 14)
  - Reid, John R. (Box 45, Folder 15)
  - Reidemeister, Kurt. (Box 45, Folder 16)
  - Reiner, John M. (Box 45, Folder 17)
  - Reiner, Markus. (Box 45, Folder 18)
  - Reininger, Robert. (Box 45, Folder 19)
  - Reiser, Oliver L. (Box 45, Folder 20)
  - Reissner, H. (Box 45, Folder 21)
  - Reisz, Eugen. (Box 45, Folder 22)
  - Renqvist, Yrjo (1 of 2). (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Renqvist, Yrjo (2 of 2). (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Requard, Fritz. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Rescher, Nicholas. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Restorff, Hedwig. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Revesz, Geza. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Richards, I.A. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Richmond, Carl A. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Richter, Hans. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Richtmyer, R.D. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Rickert, Heinrich. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Ridenour, Louis N. (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Rieger, Ladislav. (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Riemann, B. (Box 46, Folder 14)
  - Riezler, Kurt. (Box 46, Folder 15)
  - Rivier, W. (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Robbins, Herbert. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Robertson, H.P. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Robinson, Raphael M. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Roelofs, Howard D. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Rogge, Eberhard. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Roh, Franz. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Rohden, Friedrich. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Rohden, R. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Rome, Sydney C. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Romero, Francisco. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Rontgenstrahlen. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Roretz, Karl. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Rosenbaum, E.P. (Box 47, Folder 13)
  - Rosenberg, H. (Box 47, Folder 14)
  - Rosenblatt, A. (Box 47, Folder 15)
  - Rosinger, Kurt E. (Box 47, Folder 16)
  - Ross, Alf. (Box 47, Folder 17)
  - Rosser, Barkley. (Box 47, Folder 18)
  - Rosser, J.B. (Box 47, Folder 19)
  - Rossi, Mario M. (Box 47, Folder 20)
  - Roszle, Wilhelm. (Box 47, Folder 21)
  - Roth, Eugen. (Box 47, Folder 22)
  - Rothstein, Jerome. (Box 47, Folder 23)
  - Rougier, Louis. (Box 47, Folder 24)
  - Roux, Wilhelm. (Box 47, Folder 25)
  - Royden, Halsey L. (Box 47, Folder 26)
  - Rozeboom, William W. (Box 47, Folder 27)
  - Rubin, Herman. (Box 47, Folder 28)
  - Rubin, Jean E. (Box 47, Folder 29)
  - Rumer, Georg. (Box 47, Folder 30)
  - Ruska, Julius. (Box 47, Folder 31)
  - Russell, Bertrand (1 of 2). (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Russell, Bertrand (2 of 2). (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Rustow, Alexander. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Ruyer, Raymond. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Ryle, Gilbert. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Saarnio, Uuno (1 of 2). (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Saarnio, Uuno (2 of 2). (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Santillana, George de. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Sapper, R. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Sartre, Jean Paul. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Sauer, Friedrich. (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Saugstad, Per. (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Saunders, John Turk. (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Savery, William. (Box 48, Folder 14)
  - Schachter, Josef. (Box 48, Folder 15)
  - Schapiro, Meyer. (Box 48, Folder 16)
  - Schaxel, Julius. (Box 48, Folder 17)
  - Scheel, Karl. (Box 48, Folder 18)
  - Scheffler, Israel. (Box 48, Folder 19)
  - Schelling, Herman v. (Box 48, Folder 20)
  - Scherrer, Paul. (Box 48, Folder 21)
  - Schestow, Leo. (Box 48, Folder 22)
  - Schiffner, Victor. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Schiller, F.C.S. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Schilpp, Paul Arthur. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Schimank, Hans. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Schischkoff, Georgi. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Schlauk, Margaret. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Schlegel, V. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Schlomann, Alfred. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Schmidt, Arnold. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Schmitt, Charles B. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Schnuder, Erna F. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Schnell, Karl. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Schoenflies, A. (Box 49, Folder 13)
  - Scholz, Heinrich (1 of 3). (Box 49, Folder 14)
  - Scholz, Heinrich (2 of 3). (Box 49, Folder 15)
  - Scholz, Heinrich (3 of 3). (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Schonfinkel, M. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Schouten, J.A. (1 of 2). (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Schouten, J.A. (2 of 2). (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Schreber, K. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Schroder, Ernst. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Schroder, Erwin. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Schroder, Johannes. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Schroter, Karl. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Schuetz, Alfred. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Schultz, Henry. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Schultz, Julius. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Schuman, Frederick L. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Schuppe, Wilhelm. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Schwab, Joseph J. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Schwarzschild, K. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Schwayder, David S. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Schweitzer, Albert. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Scott, Dana. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Selety, Franz. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid (1 of 2). (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Sellars, Wilfrid (2 of 2). (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Sellien. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Selznick, Philip. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Senior, James K. (Box 51, Folder 14)
  - Serif, Muzaffer. (Box 51, Folder 15)
  - Servien, Pius. (Box 51, Folder 16)
  - Sesonske, Alexander. (Box 51, Folder 17)
  - Shannon, Claude E. (Box 51, Folder 18)
  - Shapley, Harlow. (Box 51, Folder 19)
  - Shebbeare, C.J. (Box 51, Folder 20)
  - Sheffer, Henry M. (Box 51, Folder 21)
  - Sheldon, W.H. (Box 51, Folder 22)
  - Sheperdson, J.C. (Box 51, Folder 23)
  - Sherif, Muzafer. (Box 51, Folder 24)
  - Shimony, Abner. (Box 51, Folder 25)
  - Shneidman, Edwin S. (Box 51, Folder 26)
  - Shorey, Paul. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Shrikhande, S.S. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Shwayder, David S. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Siedentopf, Henry. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Sigerist, Henry E. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Silberschmidt, Benno Daniel. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Simon, Herbert A. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Simon, Max. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Simons, Hans. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Singer, Edgar A. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Singer, Milton. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Sisson, Edward O. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Sivadjian, Joseph. (Box 52, Folder 13)
  - Siwek, Paulus. (Box 52, Folder 14)
  - Skinner, B.F. (Box 52, Folder 15)
  - Skolem, Th. (Box 52, Folder 16)
  - Smart, Harold R. (Box 52, Folder 17)
  - Smekal, Adolf. (Box 52, Folder 18)
  - Smith, Henry Bradford. (Box 52, Folder 19)
  - Smith, Homer W. (Box 52, Folder 20)
  - Smith, James Ward. (Box 52, Folder 21)
  - Smith T.V. (Box 52, Folder 22)
  - Smullyan, Arthur Francis. (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - Snell, Bruno. (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - Sobocinski, Boleslaw. (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - Sokolnikov, I.S. (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - Sommer, Albrecht. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Sommerfeld, Albrecht. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Somerville, John. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Sondel, Bess. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Sorokin, Pitirim A. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Spector, Clifford. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Spence, Kenneth W. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Spengler, Oswald. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Spiegelberg, Herbert. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Spielrein, J. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Spilsbury, R.J. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Spitzer, Leo. (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Sprague, R. (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Spranger, Eduard. (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Stahl, Gerold. (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Stammler, Gerhard. (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Stasiak, Stefan. (Box 53, Folder 17)
  - Steck, Max. (Box 53, Folder 18)
  - Sternberg, W. (Box 53, Folder 19)
  - Stevens, S.S. (Box 53, Folder 20)
  - Stickers, Joe. (Box 53, Folder 21)
  - Stiles, W.S. (Box 53, Folder 22)
  - Stocks, J.L. (Box 53, Folder 23)
  - Stoker, H.G. (Box 53, Folder 24)
  - Stone, Marshall H. (Box 53, Folder 25)
  - Stoops, J. Dashiell. (Box 53, Folder 26)
  - Stopes-Roe, Harry V. (Box 53, Folder 27)
  - Storer, Thomas. (Box 53, Folder 28)
  - Stouffer, Samuel A. (Box 53, Folder 29)
  - Stout, G.F. (Box 53, Folder 30)
  - Straneo, Paulo. (Box 53, Folder 31)
  - Straumann, Heinrich. (Box 53, Folder 32)
  - Strauss, Martin (1 of 2). (Box 53, Folder 33)
  - Strauss, Martin (2 of 2). (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Stromberg, Gustaf. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Struik, Dirk J. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Strum, L. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Stueckelberg, E.C.G. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Stutsman, Rachel. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Sumberg, Theodore A. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Sun, Siao-Fang. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Suppes, Patrick (1 of 2). (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Suppes, Patrick (2 of 2). (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Susani. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Suszko, Roman. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Sweden - Institute for the Theory of Science. (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Systems Development Corporation. (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Szmielew, W. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Sztejnberg, Dina. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Szivessey, G. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Takeuchi, Tokio. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Taliaferro, R. Catesby. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Tatarkiewicz, W. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Taubes, Jacob. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Tennessen, Herman. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Thaer, C. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Thayer, H.S. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Theios, John. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Thirring, Hans. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Thone, J. (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Thorndike, Edward L. (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - Thurstone, L.L. (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Tick, Leo Joseph. (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Tietze, H. (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Tingley, E.M. (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Tintner, Gerhard. (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - Tippett, L.H.C. (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - Tischner, Rudolf. (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - Tolman. Edward Chace. (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - Tomas, Vincent. (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - Tomaschek, R. (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - Toms, E. (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - Tornier, Erhard. (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - Townsend, H.G. (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - Townsend, J.S. (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - Tramer, M. (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - Triepel, Hermann. (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - Tsanoff, Radoslav A. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Tsichichold, Jan. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Tucker, Albert W. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Tufts, James H. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Tugendhat, Ernst. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Tukey, John W. (1 of 2). (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Tukey, John W. (2 of 2). (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Turhan, Mumtaz. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Turquette, Atwell R. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Tutugan, Fl. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Tymieniecka, Anna-Teresa. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Vehli, Ernst. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Uhlmann, Erich. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Uller, Karl. (Box 56, Folder 14)
  - Ullmo, J. (Box 56, Folder 15)
  - Ulmer, Josef. (Box 56, Folder 16)
  - Ulrich, Martha. (Box 56, Folder 17)
  - UNESCO. (Box 56, Folder 18)
  - Ungerer, Emil. (Box 56, Folder 19)
  - U.S. Department of State. (Box 56, Folder 20)
  - Urbach, Benno. (Box 56, Folder 21)
  - Urban, F.M. (Box 56, Folder 22)
  - Urmson, J.O. (Box 56, Folder 23)
  - Ushenko, A.P. (Box 56, Folder 24)
  - Utitz, Emil. (Box 56, Folder 25)
  - Vaccarino, di Giuseppe. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Valery, Paul. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Vallejos, M.A. Raul. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Valpola, Veli. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Van de Kamp, Peter. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Vandiver, H.S. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Vannatta, Thomas Auld. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Vanni-Rovighi, S. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Varma, Vishwanath Prasad. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Vaughan, Herbert E. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Velikovsky, Immanuel. (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Venable, Vernon. (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Vietoris, L. (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Vivas, Eliseo. (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Vogel, Th. (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Vogt, Hans. (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Vogtherr, Karl. (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Vollenhoven D.H.Th. (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Volpe, Galvano della. (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Vouillemin. (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Waehner, Trude S. (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Wajsberg, M. (1 of 2). (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Wajsberg, M. (2 of 2). (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Walker, Edwin Ruthvin. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Walter, Emil J. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Wanach, B. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Watanabi, Satosi. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Waters, Bruce. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Watson, A.G.D. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Watson, David L. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Watson, George. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Watson, John B. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Weber, J. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Webster, T.B.L. (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Weckstein, Richard L. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Weidner, Karl. (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Weigelin, G. (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Weil, Francis A. (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - Weilgart, Wolfgang. (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Weinberg, Alvin M. (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Weinberg, C.B. (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Weinberg, Julius Rudolf. (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Weinberg, Seigfried. (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Weinberger, Ottone. (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Weinmann, Rudolf. (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Weiss, Paul (1 of 2). (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Weiss, Paul (2 of 2). (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Weitz, Morris. (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Weitzenbock, Roland. (Box 58, Folder 27)
  - Weizsacker, K.F. (Box 58, Folder 28)
  - Wekstein, Louis. (Box 58, Folder 29)
  - Weller, R. (Box 58, Folder 30)
  - Wellmann, Max. (Box 58, Folder 31)
  - Wells, F.L. (Box 58, Folder 32)
  - Wells, Gardner S. (Box 58, Folder 33)
  - Wells, Rulon (1 of 2). (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Wells, Rulon (2 of 2). (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Wenzl, A. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Werkmeister. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Werner, Charles. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - West, C.P. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Weyssenhoff, J. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Wheelwright, Philip. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - White, Leslie A. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Whitehead, Alfred North. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Wick, Warner A. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Wiener, Alexander S. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Wiener, Philip P. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Willenz, Eric. (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Wind, Edgar. (Box 59, Folder 15)
  - Windred, G. (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Winthrop, Henry. (Box 59, Folder 17)
  - Wirth, Richard. (Box 59, Folder 18)
  - Wirtinger, Wilhelm. (Box 59, Folder 19)
  - Wobbermin. (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Wolf, Th. (Box 59, Folder 21)
  - Wolff, Georg. (Box 59, Folder 22)
  - Wolff, Gustav. (Box 59, Folder 23)
  - Wolfle, Dael L. (Box 59, Folder 24)
  - Woodbridge, Frederick J.E. (Box 59, Folder 25)
  - Woodger, J.H. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Wright G.H. von. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Wrinch, Dorothy. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Wulf, M. de. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Wust, Georg. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Wuster, Eugen. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Xenakis, Jason. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Yolton, John W. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Yonemitsu, Naono. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Yourgrau, Wolfgang. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Zehnder, L. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Zeisel, John. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Zerby, Lewis K. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Zerner, Friedrich. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Zich, Otakar. (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Ziegler, Heinrich Ernst. (Box 60, Folder 16)
  - Ziehen, Theodor. (Box 60, Folder 17)
  - Ziferstein, I. (Box 60, Folder 18)
  - Zipf, George Kingsley. (Box 60, Folder 19)
  - Zorn, Max. (Box 60, Folder 20)
  - Zwirner, Kurt. (Box 60, Folder 21)
  - 6 books. (Box 60)
  - 10 books. (Box 61)
  - 17 books. (Box 62)
  - 19 books. (Box 63)
  - 21 books. (Box 64)
- Books
  - Abbott, Wilton R. - Black, Max. (Box 13)
  - Bochenski - Feigl. (Box 14)
  - Feys - Hertz, P. (Box 15)
  - Heyting, A. - Lanford, C.H. & M. (Box 16)
  - Lautman, Albert - Menger, K. (Box 17)
  - Mercier - Oppenheim, Paul. (Box 18)
  - Pap, Arthur - Reichenbach, M. Hans. (Box 19)
  - Stace - Williams, D.C. (Box 20)
  - Wisdom - Zimmerman, W. (Box 21)
- Correspondence
  - between Felix Kaufmann and Carnap: Letter to Carnap 2 copies of Carnap's paper Beweis Der Unmoglichkeit Einer Gabelung Der Arithmetik. one copy is corrected; 4 sheets of manuscript with logical notations and German shorthand entitled Uber Den Goldbachscher Satz., June 19, 1927;. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hans Reichenbach: Review of Reichenbach, Axiomatik, 1924. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Paul Schilpp: entire correspondence between, 1953-59. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - J. Schlaf: letter from Carnap to Schlaf,, parodying his crazy astronomy theory. He did not answer; and a copy of Schlaf's article in Charon, 1911 May 1911. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Steinitz, Julius: Correspondence and manuscript of Steinitz Die Primar-Sekundare Doppeltrilogie Der Zahlen Als Rationale Begriffe. (in gekurzter Fassung). (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tarski, Alfred: letter from Tarski to Carnap with Carnap bibliography attached., August 7, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - The Minnesota Center Memoranda folder: containing correspondence and papers by William W. Rozeboom, Grover Maxwell, Adolf Grünbaum, P.K. Feyerabend and H. Feigl, with notes by Carnap, revisions of the authors, etc. (Box 1, Folder 7-11)
- Manuscripts (in German Shorthand) by Rudolf Carnap
  - The Aim of Inductive Logic (Stanford Congress, )., August 1960; Tape and transcript without corrections from tape. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Andere Geometrien 3, 4, 5., 1920. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Autobiography, With deletions marked in 1st version and added handwritten pages. This was the basis of the second version. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Autobiography Parts 1 and 2 and Notes for Autobiography. New (second) version., 1958.; In Carnap's handwriting: This is my own working copy with marginal remarks to be used for any further rewriting. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Axiomsystem of Inductive Logic. paragraphs 10-13. First version, 1961. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - An Axiom System of Inductive Logic. missing pp. 45, 55, 78, 108. 7 extra copies of pp. 299-399., 1959-1963. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Axiomatik Der Kausalitiat, 1923-27. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Alg. Begriffe d. Determination, 1923-27. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Begriffe, 1929-30. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Plan of vol. 1 and 2 of Einfuhring In Die Wissenschaft Philosophie (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Foundations of Mathematics, 1931. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Grundlegung Der Geometrie, 1920. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Konstitution Des Nichtgegebenen, 1929-30. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Old Manuscripts of 1931 on metalogic. The Logical Syntax book grew out of these. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Modalities (1)., 1940-42. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Modal Logic (2)., 1942. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Modal Logic (3). New and Old. [many pp. destroyed by mice nibblings on margins and whole half pages, etc.]. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Nicht-euklid. Geometrie, 1920-22. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Physik 1, 1919. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Semantica, 1938-40 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Topologie Der Raum-Zeit-Welt (k-z....) Teile 2 and 3., 1923. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Topologie Der Raum-Zeit-Welt, 1924. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Carnap Replies. 3rd proof, (for Schilpp volume)., August 1962 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Carnap Replies. final version for printer, 392 pp. (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Carnap Manuscripts for Schilpp Volume
  - Autobiography Part 1 (sec. A-G, U.) Skeleton in German shorthand, system Stolze-Schrey which can be read by Ina Carnap and Carl Hempel. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Autobiography Part 2 (section H-N, P, S, T, V) in German shorthand., 1956. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Carnap Replies. First version, with changes, deletions, and additions written in big hand. From this manuscript the revised version was typed. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Carnap Replies. First version, (typed)., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    General note
    Abraham Kaplan Repr.
  - Carnap Replies. Revised version typed, 1958. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Ayer On Other Minds (German shorthand) and a copy of Ayer's Carnap's Treatment of the Problem of Other Minds, for the Schilpp edition. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Yehoshua Bar-Hillel On (Logical Syntax, Semantics & Pragmatics). and a copy of Bar-Hillel's Remarks On Carnap's Logical Syntax Of Language, With Notes, 1957, 1954. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Carnap's notes, questions and correspondence between Arthur Benson concerning the Benson Bibliography on Carnap. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - The Arthur Benson correspondence on Carnap's Bibliography, 1954. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Beth on Constructed Language Systems, and Beth's Carnap's Views on the Advantages of Constructed Systems Over Natural Language in the Philosophy of Science, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Carnap's notes in German shorthand on Bohnert and Herbert G. Bohnert's Carnap's Theory of Definition and Analyticity (New version, Paragraph 3 added), 1955. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Arthur W. Burks' On the Significance of Carnap's System of Inductive Logic for the Philosophy of Induction., 1954.; 33 pp. (Box 7, Folder 12)